<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translation_description="App Name [CHAR LIMIT=40]">AR glTF</string>
    <string name="back_to_library">Back to Library</string>
    <string name="back">Back to Library</string>
    <string name="amphibians_are_any_organism_that_is_able_to_live_both_on_land_and_in_water">Amphibians are any organism that is able to live both on land and in water</string>
    <string name="bacteria_are_tiny_organisms_living_things_that_have_only_one_cell">Bacteria are tiny organisms (living things) that have only one cell</string>
    <string name="the_platypus_is_a_duck_billed_beaver_tailed_otter_footed_egg_laying_aquatic_creature_native_to_australia">The platypus is a duck-billed, beaver-tailed, otter-footed, egg-laying aquatic creature native to Australia</string>
    <string name="the_digestive_system_breaks_down_food_and_absorbs_nutrients_for_energy_and_growth">The digestive system breaks down food and absorbs nutrients for energy and growth.</string>
    <string name="the_heart_is_a_muscle_that_pumps_blood_to_all_parts_of_your_body_the_blood_pumped_by_your_heart_provides_your_body_with_the_oxygen_and_nutrients_it_needs_to_function">The Heart is a muscle that pumps blood to all parts of your body. The blood pumped by your heart provides your body with the oxygen and nutrients it needs to function.</string>
    <string name="refresh" />
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="reading">Reading. . .</string>
    <!-- ... other string resources ... -->
    <string name="status_ready">Ready</string>
    <string name="capture">Capture</string>
    <string name="imagepreview">ImagePreview</string>
    <string name="cells_are_the_super_tiny_building_blocks_that_make_up_all_living_things_like_plants_animals_and_even_you_they_re_so_small_you_need_a_microscope_to_see_them">Cells are the super tiny building blocks that make up all living things, like plants, animals, and even you! They\'re so small you need a microscope to see them!</string>
    <string name="biodiversity_is_all_the_different_kinds_of_life_plants_animals_and_everything_else_living_together_and_connected_in_their_environments">Biodiversity is all the different kinds of life – plants, animals, and everything else – living together and connected in their environments.</string>
    <string name="an_organism_is_any_single_thing_that_is_alive_like_a_plant_an_animal_or_even_a_tiny_bug_you_can_barely_see_if_it_eats_grows_and_can_make_more_of_itself_it_s_an_organism">An organism is any single thing that is alive, like a plant, an animal, or even a tiny bug you can barely see! If it eats, grows, and can make more of itself, it\'s an organism.</string>
    <string name="the_science_or_occupation_of_cultivating_the_soil_producing_crops_and_raising_livestock">the science or occupation of cultivating the soil, producing crops, and raising livestock</string>
    <string name="medicine_in_its_most_general_sense_refers_to_any_substance_used_to_treat_cure_prevent_or_diagnose_a_disease">Medicine, in its most general sense, refers to any substance used to treat, cure, prevent, or diagnose a disease.</string>
    <string name="reptiles_are_a_diverse_group_of_vertebrates_characterized_by_having_dry_scaly_skin_and_being_cold_blooded_they_are_typically_egg_laying_and_include_animals_like_snakes_lizards_turtles_and_crocodiles">Reptiles are a diverse group of vertebrates characterized by having dry, scaly skin and being cold-blooded. They are typically egg-laying and include animals like snakes, lizards, turtles, and crocodiles.</string>
    <string name="a_forest_is_a_place_with_lots_and_lots_of_trees_and_it_s_a_home_for_many_plants_and_animals_it_s_like_a_big_green_playground_and_a_very_important_part_of_our_earth">A forest is a place with lots and lots of trees, and it\'s a home for many plants and animals. It\'s like a big, green playground and a very important part of our Earth.</string>
    <string name="the_term_ocean_comes_from_the_latin_word_keanos_which_literally_translates_to_the_great_stream_encircling_the_earth_s_disc_this_was_used_by_the_greeks_to_describe_the_single_mass_of_water_that_they_believed_surrounded_the_earth">The term \'ocean\' comes from the Latin word “ōkeanos,” which literally translates to the “great stream encircling the earth\'s disc.” This was used by the Greeks to describe the single mass of water that they believed surrounded the earth.</string>
    <string name="a_river_is_a_big_stream_of_moving_water_that_flows_across_the_land_usually_starting_in_the_mountains_or_hills_and_flowing_towards_the_ocean_a_lake_or_another_river">A river is a big stream of moving water that flows across the land, usually starting in the mountains or hills and flowing towards the ocean, a lake, or another river.</string>
    <string name="soil_is_the_top_layer_of_the_ground_where_plants_grow_and_it_s_made_of_a_mix_of_broken_down_rocks_decaying_plants_and_tiny_living_things">Soil is the top layer of the ground where plants grow, and it\'s made of a mix of broken-down rocks, decaying plants, and tiny living things.</string>
    <string name="humans_scientifically_known_as_homo_sapiens_are_a_species_of_primate_characterized_by_bipedalism_hairlessness_and_high_intelligence">Humans, scientifically known as Homo sapiens, are a species of primate characterized by bipedalism, hairlessness, and high intelligence.</string>
    <string name="acacia_trees_are_recognized_by_their_distinctive_feathery_or_fern_like_leaves_which_can_be_either_true_leaves_or_flattened_leaf_stalks_called_phyllodes">Acacia trees are recognized by their distinctive feathery or fern-like leaves, which can be either true leaves or flattened leaf stalks called phyllodes</string>
    <string name="biological_simply_means_relating_to_life_or_living_organisms_when_we_describe_something_as_biological_we_are_saying_that_it_has_to_do_with_living_things_how_they_function_or_their_origins">biological simply means relating to life or living organisms. When we describe something as biological, we are saying that it has to do with living things, how they function, or their origins.</string>
    <string name="species_refers_to_a_group_of_similar_organisms_that_are_able_to_reproduce_this_is_part_of_how_scientists_classify_meaning_to_organize_or_compare_living_things_we_are_a_species_as_humans_and_so_are_dogs">Species refers to a group of similar organisms that are able to reproduce. This is part of how scientists classify, meaning to organize or compare living things. We are a species as humans, and so are dogs!</string>
</resources>
